let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which number should come next in the series, 48, 24, 12, ......?",
        answer: "6",
        options: [
            "8",
            "6",
            "4",
            "2",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Look at the series, 46, 44, 40, 38, 34, _, which number should come next?",
        answer: "32",
        options: ["30", "36", "32", "31"],
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which number would fill the empty space in the series; 4, 7, 12, 19, _, 39?",
        answer: "28",
        options: [
            "28",
            "26",
            "24",
            "22",
        ],
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which number would replace the underline mark in the series 20, 40, 100, _, 820?",
        answer: "280",
        options: ["240", "260", "280", "300"],
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What are the missing numbers in this series, 15, 20, 24, 15, 28, 32 15, _, _, 15?",
        answer: "36, 40",
        options: ["37, 41", "36, 40", "38, 42", "40, 44"],
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Look at the series, 77, 70, 63, 56, 49, _, which number should come next?",
        answer: "42",
        options: ["42", "46", "44", "48"],
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Look at the series; 41, 39, 35, 33, 29, _, which number should come next?",
        answer: "27",
        options: ["23", "24", "25", "27"],
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Look at the series, 1536, 384, 96, _, which number should come next?",
        answer: "24",
        options: ["24", "28", "18", "16"],
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "12 12, 24 24, 36 36, 48, _, _?",
        answer: "60",
        options: ["58", "60", "62", "64"],
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "RQP, ONM, _, IHG, FED, find the missing letters.",
        answer: "LKJ",
        options: ["CDE", "LKI", "LKJ", "BAC"],
    },
]